

# Gabriele Stefani

Date of birth: 19/01/1999

Nationality: Italian

Gender: Male

# **CONTACT**

 Via Fratelli Bandiera 32, null 50013 Campi Bisenzio, Italy



(+39) 3662816439

https://gabstevens.dev

LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ gabrielestefani/



### **ABOUT ME**

I have a Bachelor Degree in Software Engineering and I got 3 years of work expirience as a Web Developer. Now I have been leading web application projects as Team Leader. In addition I can describe myself as a flexible person with a very good attitude towards quick learning.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

01/2019 - CURRENT - Firenze, Italy

# Full Stack developer

**T&O Consulting** 

As a member of a small business I had worked on many projects:

- January 2019 May 2019: Project for QuestIT, development of a chatbot configurator, built in React.
- March 2019 July 2019: Project for Chorally, development of BI for data monitoring of Ferrovie dello Stato, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails and Elasticsearch.
- July 2019 December 2020: Project for Hepro, development of web app for booking and management of cross-border surgical operations, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- December 2019 February 2020: Project for Copernico, development of CRM for condominium administrators, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- January 2020 May 2020: Project for Law on Chain, development of a demo web app for sharing notes and messages on blockchain, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- February 2020 March 2020: Project for Travel Appeal, development of a chat system integrated with Facebook Messenger, made in Angular.
- March 2020 June 2020: Internal project, development of a system for sharing tales, built in Ruby on Rails with integrated FE in React.
- March 2020 July 2020: Project for Law on Chain, development of a blockchain-based contract management system, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- March 2020 May 2021: Project for Banca Popolare di Sondrio, development of a query system on data aggregates, built in Angular.
- March 2020 December 2021 (current): Project for StartupItalia!, development of a research and matching system between startup and investor, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- $^{\circ}$  July 2020 October 2020: Project for Streetlib, development of an electronic invoicing system, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- July 2020 January 2021: Project for Mobisec, BI development, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- January 2021 February 2020: Project for Medacta, web app maintenance, built in Ruby on Rails with integrated FE in AngularJS.
- November 2021: Project for Dream.bid, development of an auction site, built in Ruby on Rails.
- February 2021 November 2021 (current): Project for Virtual Congress, development of web app for virtual congresses, built with FE in React and BE in Ruby on Rails.
- February 2021 current: Project for Revisoft, development of a management system for accountability, built in Laravel with integrated FE in React.

 December 2021 - current: Project for Banca di Cambiano, development of home banking apps, built with BE in Java and FE in Ionic Angular.

01/06/2016 - 30/06/2016 - Firenze, Italy

# Student Internship

Comm.it s.r.l.

Internal project, development of a configurable dashboard, built in AngularJS.

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

09/2017 - 11/2020 - Florence, Italy

# **Bachelor Degree in Software Engineering**

Università degli Studi di Firenze

- September 2020: Project for Multimedia Design and Production, development of a security system with camera and motion sensor, built with FE in React and BE in Django.
- September 2020 November 2020: Project for graduation thesis, development of a semi-automatic image annotation system for the training of object recognizers, built with FE in React and BE in Django.

110/110 with honours | Development of semi-automatic annotation tools for training of object detectors based on neural networks

2012 - 2017

# **High School Diploma in Computer Science**

ITIS Antonio Meucci

94/100 | Development of an online multiplayer video game called Ungodly Kingdom, built with LibGDX in Java

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Italian

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

**English** 

<b>Listening</b> B2	<b>Reading</b> B2	Spoken production B2	Spoken interaction B2	<b>Writing</b> B2
Spanish  Listening  A1	<b>Reading</b> A1	Spoken production A1	Spoken interaction A1	<b>Writing</b> A1

# **PROJECTS**

### 01/2015

#### CircleMem

Development of a mobile video game for iOS, built in Swift.

#### 2013 - 2016

#### Lau&Max

Development of an ecommerce site, built in PHP.

# Personal Portfolio

# https://gabstevens.dev

Development of a personal portfolio, built in Gatsby.

# **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Git / JavaScript / HTML / CSS / Python / PHP / Java / TypeScript

#### **Front End**

React / Ionic / Angular / Gatsby / Material / Bootstrap **Back End** 

Ruby on Rails / Django / Laravel / PostgreSQL / MySQL

# **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

#### 05/2017

Second place at the Var Group Hackathon

### 2016

First place at Computer Science Olympics – ITIS Antonio Meucci

#### 16/05/2015

Prize Aldo Morelli – Mathesis Math Olympics

# **DRIVING LICENCE**

Driving Licence: B